Finding Aid for the Edwin Hamlett Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Nursing Materials:
  - Publications: Present Time: 32 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Present Time: 33 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Present Time: 34 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Present Time: 35 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Present Time: 36 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Present Time: 60 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Psychology Today, Jun. 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Psychology Today, Aug. 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Publications: RN, Sept. 1989 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Publications: RN, Oct. 1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Publications: RN, Jan. 1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Publications: RN, Feb. 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Publications: RT, Feb.-Mar. 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Survey of Health in Lower Income Areas of Nashville (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Publications: TN Nurse, Dec. 1991 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Publications: TN Nurse, Feb. 1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Publications: TN Nurse, Jun. 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Aug. 1976- Feb. 1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Apr., Jun. 1977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Aug., Oct. 1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Dec. 1977, Jan/Feb 1978 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Sept./Oct. 1978, Nov./Dec. 1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Mar/Apr 1979, May/Jun. 1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, May/Jun. 1978, Aug. 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Nov/Dec 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Jan/Feb 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Publications: TNA Bulletin, Mar/Apr 1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Unions and Hospitals “A Working Paper” (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Vanderbilt Gazette Vols. 18, 96, 105, 106 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Vanderbilt Gazette Vols. 107, 108, 109, 110 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Vanderbilt Gazette Vols. 111, 114, 115 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Vanderbilt Gazette Vols. 117, 118, 119, 120 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Nurse Related Newspapers (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Nurse Related Newspapers (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Nursing News Articles (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Nursing News Articles (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Nursing Miscellany (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Notes District 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Notes TNA (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Notes TNA (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Notes TNA (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Notes Re Staff Issues MCS-3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Notes University of Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Notes Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Students for a Democratic Society (SDS):
  - Correspondence, Jun. 1965- Dec. 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Directory (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Member Mailings (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - History (including Prospectus, Finances, Lists of Chapters) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - History: “Getting by with a Little Help from our Friends” by the Habers (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - History: Handbook (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - History: Port Huron Statement (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Proposals (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Proposals (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Workshops: notes and Reports from University (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Workshops: notes and Reports from National Convention (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Literature: Bibliographies and Reading Lists (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Booklets (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets/Leaflets (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters: ERAP Cairo Report, Apr. 26, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Bulletin, May 1964- Jun. 1964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Bulletin, Jan. 1965- May 1965 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Conference Daily and Viewpoints, Dec. 1965 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Worklist Mailings, July 16, 1965- Nov. 2, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Publications: Worklist Mailings, Nov. 11, 1965- Dec. 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Working Papers: Untitled- Friedman (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Working Papers: Garson- Potter (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Working Papers: Shero- Williams (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Convention Working Papers: Burlage- Garson (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Convention Working Papers: Holloway- Johnson (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Convention Working Papers: Pipkin- Shero (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Convention Working Papers: Stern- Williams (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Member Papers: Arnold- Burlage (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Member Papers: Burlage- Flacks (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Member Papers: Flacks- Hayden (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Member Papers: Ireland- VonHoffman (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Member Papers: Weisberg- Winters (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - News: New Left Notes (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Memphis Commercial Appeal, January 23, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Students Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC):
  - Correspondence: Contacts (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Incoming (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing Staff Mailings (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Releases (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - General History (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Associates: UGEQ (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Associates: UGEQ (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Automobile Materials (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Applications (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Proposals (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Meetings and Workshops (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Summer Project Reports of “Incidents” (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Legal Sized Materials (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Assorted Legal Sized Materials (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Legal Sized (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Notes (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Reports (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: Various (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters: “The Student Voice” (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: “Life with Lyndon” #’s 29, 40, 41 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Remarks and Statements (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Papers and Publications (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Pamphlets and Flyers (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Record, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Calendar, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Notes (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Newsclippings (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Southern Students Organizing Committee (SSOC):
  - Correspondence: Contacts (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Contacts/Mailing Lists (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1, 1964- Jun. 8, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jun. 21, 1964- Dec. 12, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 26, 1964- Apr. 14, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 12, 1965- Dec. 28, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 4, 1966- May 9, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May 15, 1966- Jun. 15, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Jun. 21, 1966- Oct. 10, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 26, 1966- Dec. 12, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 19, 1968- 1969 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing Pamphlets (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing News items (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - History: SSOC Brief History (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - History: Paper on SSOC, 1964-1967 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - History: SSOC and its Relation with Other Groups (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - History: Prospectus, 1967/1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - History: Handbook Spring, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - History: Guidelines (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - History: Draft Counseling Centers (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - History: Speaker’s Guide (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - History: Southern Folk Revival Project (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - History: Southern Literature “Affair” Fall, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - History: FBI Affidavit, Nov. 1964 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - History: Three Summer Projects (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - History: Dissolution Spring, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - History: Dissolution Spring, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Expense Reports (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Literature List (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Proposals Spring, 1964- Apr. 17, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Proposals: Undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Proposals: Undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Analyzing the Court System (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - The Poor in America (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Papers/Essays (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Reports by individuals: Asbury- Brosi (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Reports by individuals: Brosi- Grizzard (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Reports by individuals: Jackson- Neal (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Reports by individuals: Nolan- Steinberg (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Reports by Individuals: Terrell- Zinn (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Reports: Argument of Latin America by Carlos Fuentes (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Reports: A Brief History of Duke Employees Legal 77 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Reports: Care and Feeding of Power Structures by Jack Minnis (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Reports: Freedom and the University by Steve Weissman (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Judgment at Fort Jackson: The Trial of Howard Levy by Ira Glasser (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Reports: Mississippi’s Economics, Mississippi’s “New Image” (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Reports: Over 30 by Elizabeth Tornquist (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Reports: Southern Populism by Norman Pollack (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Reports: “SSOC” by Ron Parker, Jan. 5, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Reports: SSOC, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Reports: Student Labor and the South by Jim Williams (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Reports: University of the Status Quo by David Nolan (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Reports: Vietnam: Myth and Reality of American Policy by David Nolan (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Reports: Virginia Students Civil Rights Committee, Mar. 1965- May 1965 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Reports: Virginia Students Civil Rights Committee, Jul. 1965- Aug. 1965 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - SSOC Newsletter (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Publications: Worklist/Membership Mailings: Spring, 1966- Jun. 28, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Publications: Worklist/Membership Mailings, Nov. 18, 1967- Feb. 14, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Publications: Worklist/Membership Mailings, Mar. 2, 1968- Apr. 20, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Publications: “New Rebel” Newsletter, May 27, 1964- Oct. 1965 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - 1) Publications: “New South Student”, Nov. 1965- Oct. 1966 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Publications: “New South Student”, Nov. 1966-Feb. 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Publications: “New South Student”, Mar. 1967 (2)- Apr. 1967 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Publications: “New South Student”, Oct. 1967- Dec. 1967 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Publications: “New South Student”, Feb. 1968- Apr. 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Publications: “New South Student”, May 1968- Jan. 1969 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Christian Life Commission and National Sharecroppers Fund (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Appalachian South: vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Hermes, Jan. 1968 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Skewer: vol. 1 no. 1 and vol. 1 no. 2 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Union Workers-CONE (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Vanderbilt Divinity School (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Affiliated Organizations: Vocations for Social Change, May/June (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers/ Publications: Kudzu: vol. 2 no. 5 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers/ Publications: Nashville Breakdown: vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers/ Publications: Nashville Breakdown: vol. 1 no. 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Nov. 6-18, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Nov. 30, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Apr. 2-7, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Apr. 14-28, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Apr. 28- May 7, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, May 14- Sept. 23, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Oct. 21- Nov. 18, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Dec. 3- 10, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Jan. 19- Apr. 15, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, May 13- Oct. 15, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Oct. 28- Nov 22, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Jun 23, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Feb. 16, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Feb 18, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Virginia Weekly, Oct. 26, 1970- Feb. 8, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Virginia Weekly, Jul./Aug. 1971- Oct. 1971 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Virginia Weekly, Nov.- Dec. 1971 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Virginia Weekly, Apr.- May/Jun. 1972 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Cooleemee: Pamphlets/Flyers (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 1, 6, 7 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 9, 13, 21 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 22, 26, 27 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 31, 32, 33 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 34, 35, 42 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Cooleemee: History Loom: 43 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Cooleemee: News Articles (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Southern Research Institute (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Southern Research Institute (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Southern Research Institute (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Papers/Publications: Kansas Free Press, Mar. 22, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Campus Issues: University Reform (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Campus Issues: University Reform (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Meetings/Conferences (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Meetings/Conferences (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Meetings/Conferences (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets/Flyers (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Notes on Campus Program (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Notes (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Tennessee Council on Human Rights (TCHR):
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Mar. 1969- Dec. 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: General (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - History: General Information (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Flyers and Pamphlets (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Meetings: Agendas and Reports (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Report on Police Brutality, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Releases (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Memphis NAACP Releases (Including Hammer Report) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Reports (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, Jan. 1968- Oct. 1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, Oct. 1969- Feb. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, Mar. 1972- Jul./ Sept. 1973 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters: Fayette and Wilson County (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters: Fayette- Haywood (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Knoxville 22 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Essays by Ed (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - News Articles (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Reports, Oct. 16, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1969 Oct./Nov./Dec. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Greater Knoxville Council, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Notes, 1972 (?) (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Fayette County (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Notes: People’s Report to the Governor (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Lebanon and Wilson County (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Wilson County (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Notes: Wilson County (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Vanderbilt Divinity School:
  - Welcome Materials (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Women’s Equality At Vanderbilt (WEAV) Materials (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Welfare is a Women’s Issue (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Forstman Lectures Fall, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Publications (Various) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Impact (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets and Flyers (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Ed’s Notes: Intro to Ethics (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Ed’s Notes: Intro to Ethics (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Ed’s Notes: (miscellaneous) (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Articles (from classes, etc…) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Admissions, Awards, etc… (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Syllabi (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Various Papers (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Various Student Papers (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Various Student Papers (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Ed’s ITS Papers (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Ed’s Counter Culture Papers (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Introduction to Ethics Papers (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Papers for Models of Missionary Ministry (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Papers for Revolution Class (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Revolution Class materials (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Beisswenger Class (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Notes (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Notes (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - ITS Notes (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Introduction to Ethics Notes (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Organizations
  - AFL-CIO (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - AFS-CME (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Appalachian Committee For Full Employment (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Appalachian Committee For Full Employment (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Appalachian Economic and Political (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Boycott Grapes (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Christian Life Commission (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Council of the Southern Mountains: Pamphlets (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Council of the Southern Mountains: Newsletters (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Country Music: Pamphlets/Booklets/Miscellany (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Country Music: Pamphlets/Booklets/Miscellany (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Country Music: Pamphlets/Booklets/Miscellany (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Edgehill United Methodist Church (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Edgehill United Methodist Church (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Edgehill United Methodist Church (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Frederick Douglass Prison Movement (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Georgia Student Rural Project: Proposal (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - GI Coffee House: Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - GI Coffee House: Camp News/Newsletters (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - GI Coffee House: Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - GI Coffee House: Notes (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - GI Coffee House: Handwritten Reports/Notes (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - GI Coffee House: Night Watch Reports (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Highlander School (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Highlander School (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Labor Organizations (Multiple) (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - MDS (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Metro Human Relations Committee of Nashville (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: History (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: Memos (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: News (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: Publications (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: Publications and Pamphlets (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: Publications/Briefs (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party: Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - NAACP (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Film Society (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - National Committee against Repressive Legislation (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Personal Freedom (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - National Lawyer’s Guild (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Nonviolence Resources Center (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - North American Congress on Latin America (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Northern Student Movement (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Contacts (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Meetings (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Pamphlets/Flyers (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Pamphlets/Flyers (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Publications/Articles (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Publications/Articles (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Publications/Articles (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Newsletters (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Power: Hartsville: Notes (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity/Vista (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Oxfam (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - “Progressive” Organizations (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Project Opportunity: Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Project Opportunity: History (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Project Opportunity: 1968 Summer Program for Nelson County Virginia (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Project Opportunity: Reports (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Project Opportunity: Publications and Articles (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Project Opportunity: Pamphlets and Flyers (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Project Opportunity: Newspaper Clippings (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Project Opportunity: Notes (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Mar. 16, 1970- Aug. 3, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Oct. 1 1970- Jan. 15, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Feb. 16, 1971- Jun. 7, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Jun. 21, 1971- Oct. 4, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Nov. 15, 1971- Feb. 7, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter, Feb. 21, 1972- Jan. 22, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 3)